emporium.com 2016-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Emporium.com

This privacy policy applies only to personal information collected via this Web site, and not to any other activities of Emporium or its affiliates or companies whose products and services we sell. Personal information means information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, or credit card information, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Emporium does not own or control, or to people that Emporium does not employ or manage.

**Information**  
When visiting any Web site, your browser sends information to the site's hosting server identifying the browser you are using, your Internet Service Provider, the page you last visited, and the page you are currently visiting. We log this information and we may also track and catalog the search terms that you enter in our search forms. When you purchase a product at Emporium.com, we may collect certain information about your purchase and offer of credit (such as name, address, phone number, social security number, e-mail address and credit card and expiration date). We use this data to verify information about you and to administer and improve Emporium.com. 

**Cookies**  
We make use of a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie" to help us recognize you when you pay a repeat visit to Emporium.com. Cookies let us personalize your shopping experience based on your preferences and help Emporium.com to work better to serve you. Most browsers accept cookies. However, if you wish, you can usually set your browser to refuse cookies. If you set your browser to refuse cookies, you may not be able to submit an order online. Emporium does not use cookies to gather any personal information. 

**About Children**  
For their protection, we prohibit anyone under age 18 from submitting any information without the consent of a parent or guardian. Emporium never intentionally contacts anyone under age 18 about special offers or for marketing purposes. We refuse to sell or ship any items directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 18. 

**Security**  
We use industry-standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology, a secure server, and other physical and procedural safeguards to protect the security of your personal information. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

**Collection And Use Of Bank Account Information**  
As part of our information collection process, we may detect additional bank accounts under the ownership of the consumer. We will consider these additional accounts to be part of the application process. By applying, you authorize us to search for and evaluate bank accounts under your ownership for this purpose. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information and Third Parties**  
Emporium does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted parties who work on behalf of or with Emporium under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Emporium fulfill orders, process credit card payments, evaluate Emporium.com or communicate with you about offers from Emporium and our suppliers. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. You may opt out of future marketing communications from Emporium or our suppliers at any time by writing to us at 

Emporium  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
10920 Wilshire Blvd  
Suite 150-9138  
Los Angeles, CA 90024-6502

  * We may share information as necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We may share information when we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Emporium.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law
  * We may transfer information about you in connection with an acquisition of Emporium or a merger with another company. In this event, Emporium will notify you if information about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * We may share customer information with certain third parties such as our agents, service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as fulfilling customer orders, sending Emporium marketing communications, delivering packages, scheduling and performing installations, servicing products, maintaining our loyalty program, fulfilling subscription services, conducting research, analysis or administering surveys, sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of Emporium, processing credit card payments.
  * The third parties with whom we conduct business are authorized to use your information only to perform the service for which they are hired. They are required to abide by the terms of our Privacy Policy including taking reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure.
  * We may also share aggregated data with third parties for analysis and research purposes. This data does not contain name, address or other personally identifiable information.
  * We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our website, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails, telemarketing or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. See "Your Opt-Out Rights" below.

**Links to Other Websites and Services**  
For your convenience, our Web site may contain links to other sites. Links that appear on Emporium.com should not necessarily be deemed to imply that we endorse or have any affiliation with the linked Web sites. Emporium is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to review the separate privacy policies of each site you visit. By using Emporium.com, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy policy. If you do not agree to our policy, you may not use Emporium.com. We may change this privacy policy at any time and without prior notice. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to an e-mail address you have provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on Emporium.com so that you may be aware of our actions. Your continued use of Emporium.com following any such notice will mean that you accept such changes. 

**California Privacy Rights**  
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. 

**Your Opt-Out Rights**  
If you wish to correct, update or remove any personal information that you have provided through Emporium.com, please write us at: 

Emporium  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
10920 Wilshire Blvd  
Suite 150-9138  
Los Angeles, CA 90024-6502
